{
  "shortDescription": "Fun quiz about celebs and pets!",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Beyonce's birth year?",
      "answers": ["1981", "1982", "1983"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Oldest dog breed?",
      "answers": ["Basenji", "Beagle", "Bulldog"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Most streams?",
      "answers": ["Drake", "Bieber", "Swift"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Harry Styles' birth year?",
      "answers": ["1993", "1994", "1995"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Smallest cat breed?",
      "answers": ["Sphynx", "Munchkin", "Bengal"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Adele's Grammy year?",
      "answers": ["2016", "2017", "2018"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Avg dog lifespan?",
      "answers": ["10", "13", "15"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "The Weeknd's birth year?",
      "answers": ["1989", "1990", "1991"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Most popular dog?",
      "answers": ["Labrador", "Poodle", "Beagle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Billie Eilish's Grammy?",
      "answers": ["Bad Guy", "Ocean", "Bored"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Cats' sleep hours?",
      "answers": ["12", "14", "16"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "First Grammy?",
      "answers": ["Swift", "Eilish", "Lizzo"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Ed Sheeran birth year?",
      "answers": ["1990", "1991", "1992"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Cats' whiskers?",
      "answers": ["20", "24", "28"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Drake's Grammy year?",
      "answers": ["2017", "2018", "2019"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Selena Gomez born?",
      "answers": ["1991", "1992", "1993"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Highest streams?",
      "answers": ["Rihanna", "Grande", "Bieber"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Shawn Mendes' birth year?",
      "answers": ["1997", "1998", "1999"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Smartest dog?",
      "answers": ["Border", "Poodle", "Retriever"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
